Guide to the Stevens family papers, [ca. 1775-2010]
Stevens family papers, [ca. 1775-2010]
- Series IV. Robert Sproule Stevens Generation
  - IV-E. Marian Stevens (1885-1975)
    - Artwork
      - Newspaper "Maplewood Farm News," written and drawn by Marian Stevens, 1918 (Box 76, Folder 9)
      - Silver medallion from the Corcoran Gallery, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Series V. Robert Croll Stevens Generation
  - V-A. Robert Croll Stevens (b. 1924)
    - Personal and Academic Papers
      - Baby book, 1924 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Essay - "Around The World", 1935-36 (Box 43*, Folder 1)
      - Trip around the world: typescript of diary and reminiscences, 1935-36 (Box 43*, Folder 2)
      - Original diary - Trip Around The World, 1935-36 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - Typescript of Trip Around The World diary, 1935-36 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - Transcript of Trip Around The World diary, 1935-36 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Trip around the world: original letters and, 1935-36 (Box 43*, Folder 3)
      - Newspaper clippings of family interest, 1940-53 (Box 43*, Folder 4)
      - Notes for music class, 1940 (Box 43*, Folder 5)
      - Academic papers, 1940-41 (Box 43*, Folder 6)
      - Academic papers, 1941 (Box 43*, Folder 7)
      - Academic papers, 1942 (Box 43*, Folder 8)
      - Academic papers, 1942 (Box 43*, Folder 9)
      - Daily reminder book, 1943 (Box 43*, Folder 10)
      - Daily reminder book, 1944 (Box 43*, Folder 11)
      - Bausch & Lomb Medal, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - WWII Misc: mileage ration, Air Raid Warden arm band; blood donor certificate, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Newspaper: Parsons Sun -"City Founder Focus of Research", May 4-5, 1991 (Box 26, Folder -)
    - Correspondence
      - Correspondence, 1914-1925 (Box 43*, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence: ananchronisms to and from RCS, 1934 and 1943 (Box 43*, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence: family letters to RCS, Pre-1936 (Box 43*, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence: sympathy letters to RCS upon his mother's death, Sep-36 (Box 43*, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 43*, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, 1937-1939 (Box 43*, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence: RSpS to RCS at Hackley, Sept-Dec 1936 (Box 43*, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence: RSpS to RCS at Hackley, 1936-1937 (Box 43*, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence: RSpS to RCS at Hackley, Jan-May 1937 (Box 43*, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence: RSpS to RCS at Hackley, 1937-1938 (Box 43*, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence: RSpS to RCS at Hackley, 1937-1938 (Box 43*, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence: Ellen Carey to RCS at Hackley, 1936-1937 (Box 43*, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence: Dorothea Stevens to RCS at Hackley, 1936-1938 (Box 43*, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence: Dorothea Stevens and Uncle Fred to RCS at Hackley, 1936-1938 (Box 43*, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 43*, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence: miscellaneous, mostly undated, 1937-1940? (Box 43*, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence (legal size), 1938-1939 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Holiday cards, mostly undated: birthday, Easter, Valentine's Day, 1939-? (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence: Family and friends to RCS at Andover, Fall 1939 (Box 44*, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence: Family and friends to RCS at Andover, Fall 1939 (Box 44*, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence: Friends and family to RCS, Fall 1939 (Box 44*, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence: Friends and family to RCS, April-June 1940 (Box 44*, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence: Friends and family to RCS, April-June 1940 (Box 44*, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence: Friends and family to RCS, April-June 1940 (Box 44*, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 44*, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence: Friends and family to RCS, Jan-March 1941 (Box 44*, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence: Friends and family to RCS (graduation from Andover), April-June 1941 (Box 44*, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence: Friends and family to RCS, Autumn 1941 (Box 44*, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence: Eva to RCS, some undated, Autumn 1941 (Box 44*, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, July 1941 - April 1942 (Box 44*, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Summer 1942 (Box 44*, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence: Harvard, Mid-late summer 1942 (Box 44*, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence: moving to DC, Spring-summer 1942 (Box 44*, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence: Christmas, 1942 (Box 44*, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence: Eva, RSS, and Anne (Holidays), 1942 (Box 44*, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence: letters from Anne, 1942 (Box 44*, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 44*, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 44*, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 44*, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 44*, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence: to RCS, including "N" pin, some undated 1943, 12/14/1942, 1/20/1943 - 2/28/1943 (Box 44*, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, 3/1/1943 - 3/17/1943 (Box 44*, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, 3/18/1943 - 4/5/1943 (Box 44*, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, 4/12/1943 - 5/12/1943 (Box 44*, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, 5/17/1943 - 5/29/1943 (Box 44*, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, 6/2/1941 - 6/17/1943 (Box 44*, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence, 6/20/1943 - 7/15/1943 (Box 44*, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, 7/16/1943 - 7/28/1943 (Box 44*, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, 7/30/1943 - 8/17/1943 (Box 44*, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, 8/20/1943 - 8/31/1943 (Box 44*, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence, 9/1/1943 - 9/28/1943 (Box 44*, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence, 10/1/1943 - 10/31/1943 (Box 44*, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, 11/1/1943 - 11/17/1943 (Box 44*, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, 11/18/1943 - 12/10/1943 (Box 44*, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, 12/13/1943 - 12/24/1943 (Box 44*, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence: Christmas greetings, Dec-43 (Box 44*, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence, 12/17/1943 - 12/30/1943 (Box 44*, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence, 1/3/1944 - 1/30/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence, 2/1/1944 - 2/13/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence, 2/14/1944 - 2/29/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 42)
      - Correspondence, 3/1/1944 - 3/27/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 43)
      - Correspondence, 4/2/1944 - 4/20/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 44)
      - Correspondence, 4/22/1944 - 5/14/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 45)
      - Correspondence, 5/15/1944 - 6/12/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 46)
      - Correspondence, 6/14/1944 - 6/29/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence, 7/2/1944 - 7/10/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 48)
      - Correspondence, 7/16/1944 - 7/28/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 49)
      - Correspondence, 8/2/1944 - 8/8/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 50)
      - Correspondence, 8/8/1944 - 8/21/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 51)
      - Correspondence, 8/25/1944 - 9/26/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 52)
      - Correspondence, 10/1/1944 - 10/6/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 53)
      - Correspondence, 10/15/1944 - 10/30/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 54)
      - Correspondence, 11/2/1944 - 11/21/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 55)
      - Correspondence, 11/26/1944 - 12/4/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 56)
      - Correspondence, 12/4/1944 - 12/26/1944 (Box 44*, Folder 57)
      - Correspondence, 12/9/1944 - 1/13/1945 (Box 44*, Folder 58)
      - Correspondence, 1/15/1945 - 1/30/1945 (Box 44*, Folder 59)
      - Correspondence, 2/1/1945 - 2/23/1945 (Box 44*, Folder 60)
      - Correspondence, 2/26/1945 - 3/12/1945 (Box 44*, Folder 61)
      - Correspondence, 3/15/1945 - 4/4/1945 (Box 44*, Folder 62)
      - Correspondence, 4/4/1945 - 4/16/1945 (Box 44*, Folder 63)
      - Correspondence, 4/19/1945 - 5/5/1945 (Box 44*, Folder 64)
      - Correspondence, 5/6/1945 - 6/5/1945 (Box 45*, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 6/16/1945 - 7/10/1945 (Box 45*, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 7/11/1945 - 8/10/1945 (Box 45*, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 8/11/1945 - 8/31/1945 (Box 45*, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 9/8/1945 - 9/15/1945 (Box 45*, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 9/23/1945 - 9/29/1945 (Box 45*, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 9/30/1945 - 10/1/1945 (Box 45*, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 10/2/1945 - 10/7/1945 (Box 45*, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 10/8/1945 - 10/11/1945 (Box 45*, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, 10/15/1945 - 10/31/1945 (Box 45*, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, 11/1/1945 - 11/13/1945 (Box 45*, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 11/15/1945 - 11/25/1945 (Box 45*, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 11/26/1945 - 11/30/1945 (Box 45*, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, 12/1/1945 - 12/10/1945 (Box 45*, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, 12/12/1945 - 12/31/1945 (Box 45*, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, 1/1/1946 - 1/15/1946 (Box 45*, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, 1/15/1946 - 1/26/1946 (Box 45*, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, 2/1/1946 - 2/10/1946 (Box 45*, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, 2/11/1946 - 2/28/1946 (Box 45*, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, 3/1/1946 - 3/16/1946 (Box 45*, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, 3/20/1946 - 4/8/1946 (Box 45*, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, 4/10/1946 - 5/9/1946 (Box 45*, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, 5/12/1946 - 5/27/1946 (Box 45*, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, 6/1/1946 - 7/12/1946 (Box 45*, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, 7/15/1946 - 8/1/1946 (Box 45*, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, 8/1/1946 - 8/31/1946 (Box 45*, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, 9/1/1946 - 10/3/1946 (Box 45*, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, 10/4/1946 - 10/21/1946 (Box 45*, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence, 10/23/1946 - 11/14/1946 (Box 45*, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, 11/19/1946 - 12/31/1946 (Box 45*, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, 1/2/1947 - 1/27/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, 2/4/1947 - 3/1/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence, 3/2/1947 - 3/25/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence, 3/27/1947 - 4/13/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, 4/14/1947 - 5/10/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, 5/11/1947 - 5/27/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, 6/2/1947 - 6/16/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence, 6/17/1947 - 7/10/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence, 7/15/1947 - 7/22/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence, 7/23/1947 - 8/5/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence, 8/7/1947 - 8/14/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence, 8/18/1947 - 9/13/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 42)
      - Correspondence, 9/16/1947 - 9/28/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 43)
      - Correspondence, 10/3/1947 - 10/15/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 44)
      - Correspondence, 10/18/1947 - 10/30/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 45)
      - Correspondence: Jane Knauss to RCS, 10/27/1947 - 12/30/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 46)
      - Correspondence, 11/2/1947 - 11/19/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence, 11/20/1947 - 12/6/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 48)
      - Correspondence, 12/7/1947 - 12/10/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 49)
      - Correspondence, 12/11/1947 - 12/26/1947 (Box 45*, Folder 50)
      - Correspondence: Jane Knauss to RCS, 1/2/1948 - 1/30/1948 (Box 45*, Folder 51)
      - Correspondence, 1/7/1948 - 1/14/1948 (Box 45*, Folder 52)
      - Correspondence, 1/15/1948 - 1/26/1948 (Box 45*, Folder 53)
      - Correspondence, 1/27/1948 - 2/14/1948 (Box 45*, Folder 54)
      - Correspondence: Jane Knauss to RCS, 2/1/1948 - 2/29/1948 (Box 45*, Folder 55)
      - Correspondence, 2/15/1948 - 3/14/1948 (Box 45*, Folder 56)
      - Correspondence: Jane Knauss to RCS, 3/1/1948 - 3/16/1948 (Box 45*, Folder 57)
      - Correspondence, 3/15/1948 - 3/31/1948 (Box 45*, Folder 58)
      - Correspondence: Jane Knauss to RCS, 3/24/1948 - 4/1/1948 (Box 45*, Folder 59)
      - Correspondence, 4/1/1948 - 4/20/1948 (Box 45*, Folder 60)
      - Correspondence, 4/27/1948 - 5/13/1948 (Box 45*, Folder 61)
      - Correspondence: Jane Knauss to RCS - Engagement, April 1948 - May 18, 1948 (Box 45*, Folder 62)
      - Correspondence: Engagement/Graduation, 1948 (Box 45*, Folder 63)
      - Correspondence: Wedding preparations, 1948 (Box 45*, Folder 64)
      - Correspondence: Wedding telegrams, 24-Jul-48 (Box 45*, Folder 65)
      - Wedding/Graduation clippings, 1948 (Box 45*, Folder 66)
      - Wedding keepsakes, 1948 (Box 45*, Folder 67)
      - Correspondence: Wedding/Anniversary letters, cards, telegrams, 1948-1949 (Box 45*, Folder 68)
      - Correspondence: First Wedding Anniversary, Birth of Nancy Dunbar Stevens, 1949-1950 (Box 45*, Folder 69)
      - Correspondence: Arrival of Nancy Dunbar Stevens, Feb-Mar 1950 (Box 45*, Folder 70)
    - Business Records
      - Papers/write-ups from Lewis case, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Asam Manufacturing Company records, 1953-54 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Asam Mnfng. Co. records, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Asam Mnfng. Co. records, 1956 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Asam Mnfng. Co. records, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Asam Mnfng. Co. records, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Asam Mnfng. Co. general correspondence, 1956-58 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Asam Mnfng. Co. correspondence: pinion shaft, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Asam Mnfng. Co. general correspondence, 1959-62 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Employment history with Stromberg-Carlson, 1954-64 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - Employment history with Stromberg-Carlson, 1965-70 (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - Stromberg-Carlson: Golden Rule, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - Stromberg-Carlson advertisement brochures, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 16)
      - Stromberg-Carlson advertisements, 1955-57 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - Stromberg-Carlson vendor rating system, 1956 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - "Stromberg-Carlson News", 1961-69 (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - General Dynamics/Electronics: Rochester purchasing training course, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - Stromberg-Carlson purchasing department non-stock forms, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 21)
      - Stromberg-Carlson misc personal, 1963-71 (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - Stromberg-Carlson Liquid Carbonic Case, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - Stromberg-Carlson Zero Defects Program, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 24)
      - "Challenges of Ethics" class, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 25)
      - Stromberg-Carlson welcome pamphlets, 1967-69 (Box 42, Folder 26)
      - Stromberg-Carlson government quality system requirements, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 27)
      - Stromberg-Carlson Traffic Routing Guide, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 28)
      - Stromberg-Carlson Purchasing Manual, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 29)
      - Stromberg-Carlson Purchasing Department desk instructions, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 30)
      - Stromberg-Carlson branch interviews, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 31)
      - Termination from Stromberg-Carlson, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 32)
      - Resume versions, 1959-1972 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Financial Papers
      - Correspondence related to donation of Knauss Paradox Lake Property, 1971-1975 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Papers related to Paradox Land and tax information, 1975-1992 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Attica Historical Society, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence: Kansas State Historical Society, 1989-1993 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Misc. financial papers, 1961-1996 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - V-B. Jane Eleanor Knauss Stevens (b. 1925)
    - Resume versions, 1961-1965 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Silk ties with logo for the Cornell Graduate School of Business and Public Administration, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - "Auto-Bob-ography", 2009 (Box 90)
- Series VI. Genealogy Research and Allied Families
  - VI-A. Robert Croll Stevens Research Files
    - Achilles - C.W.B. Smith, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Aldrich, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Allen, 1888, 1891 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Annis, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Antram, 1977, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Arneson, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Atherton (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Bahret, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Bahret, Alfred, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Bahret, Edward, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Bahret, John Henry, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Bahret, Robert, 1984-1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Baker, John, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Baker, Nancy Dunbar (Stevens), 1980-1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Bangs, Edward, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Barrows, Caroline: Correspondence, 1963-1983 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Bates, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Bearse, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Benjamin, 1947-1991, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
    - Bennett, 1904 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Beurer, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Binetsch, Rev. Albrecht, 1984-1991 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Binetsch, Richard S., 1984-1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Bishop, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Bliss, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Bond, Thomas, 1855-1960, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Booth (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Boudinot, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Bourton, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Bradley, 1878, 1915, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Bradley, Mrs. Lyman S. (Laura G.): Photocopies, 1887, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Brandt, 1977-1980 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Brewster, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Bronson (Brownson), 1962 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Brooke, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Brown, Christian, 1868-1954, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Brown, Marie Bahret, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Brown, William, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Bullard, 1928, 1930, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Bunn, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Burnett, Frances L.: Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Burr, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Bushnell, 1945, 1985, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Butcher, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Butler, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Campbell, Alice Bahret, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Catlin, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Chapman, 1931, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Chase, 1868-1963, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Chesire, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Chilton, 1978, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Church, 1887, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Churchill, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Clark, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Clough, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Cogswell, 1943-1959, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Colby, 1939, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Conant, 1887 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Cook, Ruth S. (Mrs. Douglas), 1984-1987 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Cooke, 1866, 1898, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Cormier, Martha Elizabeth (Nickse), 1984-1990 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Cornish, Sandra, 1952-1989 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Croll, 1977-1980 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Croll (oversized item), n.d. (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Croll, 1980-1988 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Croll, Albert I. and Sarah H., 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Croll, Clarence G., 1933, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Croll, Lawrence W., 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Croll, Lawrence W., 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Dane, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Darlington, Jean (Reynolds), 1979-1983 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Davis, 1966-1977 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Davis, James, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Davis, Robert, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - DeFriez, Albert Ivins Croll, 1980-1990 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - DeFriez, Grace Croll, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - DeFriez, Nicholas Ivins, 1984-1988 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - DeFriez, Thaddeus Coffin, n.d. (1918) (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Deming, 1904, 1915 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Dunbar, 1907-1983 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Dunbar (oversized item), 1903 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Dunbar, 1986-1990 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Dunham, 1907 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Easton, Joyce, 1949-1990 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Eaton, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Eddy, 1881, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Ellery, 1943, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Eveleth, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Everingham, 1982-1984 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Farrington, 1976-1981 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Fellows, n.d., 1926 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Feyerabend, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Field, 1901, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Fish, Mary Ann (Knauss), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Fisher, n.d., 1919 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Floyd, 1970-1975 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Foote, 1975-1991 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Freeman, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - French, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - French, 1891, 1917 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Garber, 1977-1980 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Gaunt, 1977-1983 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Gaylard/Gaylord, 1892-1989 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Gibson, Elizabeth DeFriez, 1984-1990 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Glover, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Goodhue, 1891, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Gould, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Gray, Pauline DeFriez, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Gregory, Dudley, 1914-1991 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Gregory, Dudley: E.W.D. Stevens, trustee, 1959-1966 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Gross, Jeanne (Sommer), 1984-1990 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Gulick, F. Martin, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Haas, Dieter, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Hall, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Halstead, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Hammond, 1974-1982 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Hanna, Robert, 1880 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Harding, Jos., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Harding, Thomas, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Harris/Latham/Lathrop, 1897, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Hastings, 1950-1977 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Hawes, n.d., 1941 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Hawkes, 1957, 1980, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Hayes, Tracey, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Hayward, Thomas, 1897, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Hayward, William, n.d., 1948 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Heath, 1910-1977 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Hicks, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Higgins, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Hills, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Hindenburg, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Hise, June Beckley, 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Hofmann, Gerhard, 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Hogaboom, Marilyn, 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Hollister, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Hopkins, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Howe/Loomis, 1979-1989 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Howe/Loomis (oversized items) (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Howes, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Howland (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Hunt, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Hunter/Merrill (Smith line), 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Hurlbut, n.d., 1888 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Ingells, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Ingersoll, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Ivins, 1977-1987 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Jessup, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Johnson, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Johnson, n.d., 1983 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Kelham, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Kent, 1976-1983 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Keyes, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Killam/Kilham/Pickworth, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Kingsley, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Klein, 1977, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Kling/Windmüller (Binetsch), 1984-1990 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Knauss, 1893-1956 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Knauss, 1964-1986 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Knauss, 1986-1990 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Knauss Bros. history, 1951-1987 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Knauss family - Coat of Arms, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Knauss, Charles William, 1987-1990 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Knauss, Clifford, 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Knauss, Clifford D., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Knauss, David W., 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Knauss, Donald, 1984-1987 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Knauss, Edgar, 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Knauss, Elizabeth, 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Knauss, Ernst, 1928, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Knauss, Eugen, 1984-1990 (Box 14, Folder 61-62)
    - Knauss, Frederick L., 1984-1991 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Knauss, Gordon, 1984-1990 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Knauss, Hans, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Knauss, Herman, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 64)